relaythat.com 2016-12-25

# RELAY

Welcome to RELAY, the website and online service of RELAY Inc. ("us", "we", or "our"). Our Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, and protect information that applies to our Service, and your choices about the collection and use of your information. Capitalized terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meaning given them in our Terms of Use relaythat.com/terms_of_use.

##### User Information

RELAY collect the user's email for the main purpose of login credential. RELAY also use the user provided email for sending batch processed User Content. The user’s email is also our main channel for notification. Email information can be update with the user’s account settings page. RELAY requires all users to verify their email at initial sign up and subsequent modifications.

RELAY utilizes credit card information for payments of our Service. User’s credit card information is handed by our client side application to our payment processor [Stripe](https://stripe.com/). RELAY will never store any credit card information. Furthermore will never pass any credit card information to our server. [Stripe](https://stripe.com/) stores the user’s credit card information for the purpose of automatic renewal at the end of subscription period. Please refer to user account setting page to determine the user's renewal date, and for turning off automatic renewal. We collect billing address for verification against credit card fraud. The user's shipping address may be provided for recieving gift merchandise. RELAY will never send unsolicited material via mail. 

Upon connecting third party services e.g. Facebook, Twitter, etc. to RELAY, access token for such services' authentication is store by RELAY. Access token e.g. Facebook UID allow our Service to publish User Content on the user's behalf and only when request by the user. These tokens may also grant RELAY with additional permissions with the User's discretion to tailor our services base on data e.g. Facebook Likes, Twitter Following, and others.

We utilize third party tools to help us track and improve your user experience. Information of IP, Location, Gender are reported to us by third party platforms such as Google Analytics. We do not store your location and other personal information derived from third party apis. We do store IP addresses for security purpose, in case of abuse (action against the terms of use policy)

RELAY use encrypted cookie on you browser to maintain a user's session. Cookie is required for the full RELAY experience. Disabling may cause sign in to be required after each user action. Also many user preferences will not be record for future use. Logging of user activity is archived for analysis. These analysis include product usage behavior, temporal traffic behavior, and etc. Logging information is used by us solely for purpose of improving our server performance.

##### Sharing your information

We will not rent or sell your information into third parties outside RELAY and its group companies (including any parent, subsidiaries and affiliates) without your consent, except as noted in this. We may share your information with third-party business partners for the purpose of providing the Service to you. Those business partners will be given limited access to your information as is reasonably necessary to deliver the Service, and we will require that such third parties comply with this Privacy Policy.

##### Sharing of your User Content

Any User content that you input into the Service is only accessible by you. Any content exported from the service will be the responsibility of the user. Users may request to have their User Content purged from our system. For User Content removal please contact us at [support@relaythat.com](mailto:support@relaythat.com)

##### Share your information with authority

RELAY will disclose your information where required to do so by law or subpoena or if we reasonably believe that such action is necessary to (a) comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement; (b) to enforce our Terms of Use or to protect the security or integrity of our Service; and/or (c) to exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of RELAY, our Users or others.

##### Advertisements On RELAY

We will never have paid advertisement on RELAY. Our application is meant as a tool for our subscribers to create digital graphics with their User Content more efficiently and effectively. In other words advertisement will reduce the efficiency of the software, thus will never be included.

##### Advertisement For RELAY

We will periodically send out promotional emails to our User. These emails can be avoided by changing the user account setting. We will also utilize third party advertisers to promote our product. These third party promotion can be driven by the data gathered by RELAY.

##### Data Storage

RELAY lease third party cloud computing platforms e.g. Amazon Web Services for storage of data and hosting of web services. We can not guarantee data integrity and security on the behalf of these cloud platforms. Please refer to their security and privacy policy for additional information on the security of your data. On the client side your information can be cache by the browser. We are not responsible for the security of client information. User may delete browser cache, and cookie to further ensure data security. 

##### Data Storage Security

RELAY cares about the security of your information, and uses commercially reasonable safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of all information collected through the Service. To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you access to your account. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information, and for controlling access to your email communications from RELAY, at all times. However, RELAY cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to RELAY or guarantee that information on the Service may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed. Your privacy settings may also be affected by changes to the functionality of third party sites and services that you add to the RELAY Service, such as social networks. RELAY is not responsible for the functionality or security measures of any third party.

##### Compromise of information

In the event that any information under our control is compromised as a result of a breach of security, RELAY will take reasonable steps to investigate the situation and where appropriate, notify those individuals whose information may have been compromised and take other steps, in accordance with any applicable laws and regulations. 

##### User Tracking

RELAY consistently track each user's page visits and click interaction within the scope of our domain. The tracking data will never be associated to identifiable personal information. We may share tracking data with third party business partner for providing services. 

##### Children’s privacy

RELAY does not knowingly collect or solicit any information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register as Users. The Service and its content are not directed at children under the age of 13. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [support@relaythat.com](mailto:support@relaythat.com).

##### External Links

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites or services linked to or from the Service, including the information or content contained therein. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to third-party websites or services. Your browsing and interaction on any third-party website or service, including those that have a link or advertisement on our website, are subject to that third party’s own rules and policies. In addition, you agree that we are not responsible for and we do not exercise control over any third-parties that you authorize to access your User Content. If you are using a third-party website or service (like Facebook) and you allow such a third-party access to your User Content you do so at your own risk. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from other sources other than through the Service.

##### Changes to our Privacy Policy

RELAY may modify or update this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect the changes in our business and practices, and so you should review this page periodically.
